[
    {
        "username": "islam",
        "category": "basics",
        "date": "2025-01-16 15:39:07",
        "score": 1,
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "Quel type de données est utilisé pour représenter du texte en Python ?",
                "user_response": "int",
                "correct_response": "str"
            },
            {
                "question": "What keyword is used to define a variable in Python?",
                "user_response": "var",
                "correct_response": "No keyword needed"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the output of '3 + 2 * 2' in Python?",
                "user_response": "10",
                "correct_response": "7"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of these is a valid Python identifier?",
                "user_response": "variable_1",
                "correct_response": "variable_1"
            },
            {
                "question": "How do you get the length of a string in Python?",
                "user_response": "length()",
                "correct_response": "len()"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "username": "islam",
        "category": "data_structures",
        "date": "2025-01-16 15:39:44",
        "score": 3,
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "Quelle est la méthode correcte pour ajouter un élément à une liste en Python ?",
                "user_response": "add()",
                "correct_response": "append()"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which data type is used to store a sequence of characters?",
                "user_response": "tuple",
                "correct_response": "string"
            },
            {
                "question": "How do you create a list in Python?",
                "user_response": "[]",
                "correct_response": "[]"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the correct syntax for a dictionary in Python?",
                "user_response": "{key: value}",
                "correct_response": "{key: value}"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which method is used to remove an item from a set?",
                "user_response": "remove()",
                "correct_response": "remove()"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "username": "islam",
        "category": "basics",
        "date": "2025-01-16 15:47:02",
        "score": 1,
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "Quel type de données est utilisé pour représenter du texte en Python ?",
                "user_response": "str",
                "correct_response": "str"
            },
            {
                "question": "What keyword is used to define a variable in Python?",
                "user_response": "Pas de réponse",
                "correct_response": "No keyword needed"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the output of '3 + 2 * 2' in Python?",
                "user_response": "Pas de réponse",
                "correct_response": "7"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of these is a valid Python identifier?",
                "user_response": "Pas de réponse",
                "correct_response": "variable_1"
            },
            {
                "question": "How do you get the length of a string in Python?",
                "user_response": "Pas de réponse",
                "correct_response": "len()"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "username": "islam",
        "category": "basics",
        "date": "2025-01-16 15:48:18",
        "score": 3,
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "Quel type de données est utilisé pour représenter du texte en Python ?",
                "user_response": "str",
                "correct_response": "str"
            },
            {
                "question": "What keyword is used to define a variable in Python?",
                "user_response": "Pas de réponse",
                "correct_response": "No keyword needed"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the output of '3 + 2 * 2' in Python?",
                "user_response": "7",
                "correct_response": "7"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of these is a valid Python identifier?",
                "user_response": "Pas de réponse",
                "correct_response": "variable_1"
            },
            {
                "question": "How do you get the length of a string in Python?",
                "user_response": "len()",
                "correct_response": "len()"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "username": "lolo",
        "category": "data_structures",
        "date": "2025-01-16 15:49:58",
        "score": 1,
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "Quelle est la méthode correcte pour ajouter un élément à une liste en Python ?",
                "user_response": "add()",
                "correct_response": "append()"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which data type is used to store a sequence of characters?",
                "user_response": "list",
                "correct_response": "string"
            },
            {
                "question": "How do you create a list in Python?",
                "user_response": "[]",
                "correct_response": "[]"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the correct syntax for a dictionary in Python?",
                "user_response": "Pas de réponse",
                "correct_response": "{key: value}"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which method is used to remove an item from a set?",
                "user_response": "Pas de réponse",
                "correct_response": "remove()"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "username": "test",
        "category": "basics",
        "date": "2025-01-16 15:55:36",
        "score": 2,
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "Quel type de données est utilisé pour représenter du texte en Python ?",
                "user_response": "str",
                "correct_response": "str"
            },
            {
                "question": "What keyword is used to define a variable in Python?",
                "user_response": "let",
                "correct_response": "No keyword needed"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the output of '3 + 2 * 2' in Python?",
                "user_response": "Pas de réponse",
                "correct_response": "7"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of these is a valid Python identifier?",
                "user_response": "Pas de réponse",
                "correct_response": "variable_1"
            },
            {
                "question": "How do you get the length of a string in Python?",
                "user_response": "len()",
                "correct_response": "len()"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "username": "abdou",
        "category": "basics",
        "date": "2025-01-22 19:08:57",
        "score": 3,
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "Quel type de données est utilisé pour représenter du texte en Python ?",
                "user_response": "str",
                "correct_response": "str"
            },
            {
                "question": "What keyword is used to define a variable in Python?",
                "user_response": "No keyword needed",
                "correct_response": "No keyword needed"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the output of '3 + 2 * 2' in Python?",
                "user_response": "10",
                "correct_response": "7"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of these is a valid Python identifier?",
                "user_response": "variable_1",
                "correct_response": "variable_1"
            },
            {
                "question": "How do you get the length of a string in Python?",
                "user_response": "size()",
                "correct_response": "len()"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "username": "admin",
        "category": "basics",
        "date": "2025-01-22 19:10:20",
        "score": 3,
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "Quel type de données est utilisé pour représenter du texte en Python ?",
                "user_response": "str",
                "correct_response": "str"
            },
            {
                "question": "What keyword is used to define a variable in Python?",
                "user_response": "No keyword needed",
                "correct_response": "No keyword needed"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the output of '3 + 2 * 2' in Python?",
                "user_response": "10",
                "correct_response": "7"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of these is a valid Python identifier?",
                "user_response": "variable_1",
                "correct_response": "variable_1"
            },
            {
                "question": "How do you get the length of a string in Python?",
                "user_response": "size()",
                "correct_response": "len()"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "username": "admin",
        "category": "basics",
        "date": "2025-01-22 19:14:59",
        "score": 6,
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "Quel type de données est utilisé pour représenter du texte en Python ?",
                "user_response": "str",
                "correct_response": "str"
            },
            {
                "question": "What keyword is used to define a variable in Python?",
                "user_response": "No keyword needed",
                "correct_response": "No keyword needed"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the output of '3 + 2 * 2' in Python?",
                "user_response": "7",
                "correct_response": "7"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of these is a valid Python identifier?",
                "user_response": "variable_1",
                "correct_response": "variable_1"
            },
            {
                "question": "How do you get the length of a string in Python?",
                "user_response": "len()",
                "correct_response": "len()"
            },
            {
                "question": "comment définit-on un commentaire dans le code ?",
                "user_response": "# Commentaire",
                "correct_response": "# Commentaire"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "username": "admin",
        "category": "basics",
        "date": "2025-01-22 19:40:43",
        "score": 6,
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "Quel type de données est utilisé pour représenter du texte en Python ?",
                "user_response": "str",
                "correct_response": "str"
            },
            {
                "question": "What keyword is used to define a variable in Python?",
                "user_response": "No keyword needed",
                "correct_response": "No keyword needed"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the output of '3 + 2 * 2' in Python?",
                "user_response": "7",
                "correct_response": "7"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of these is a valid Python identifier?",
                "user_response": "variable_1",
                "correct_response": "variable_1"
            },
            {
                "question": "How do you get the length of a string in Python?",
                "user_response": "len()",
                "correct_response": "len()"
            },
            {
                "question": "En Python, comment définit-on un commentaire dans le code ?",
                "user_response": "# Commentaire",
                "correct_response": "# Commentaire"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "username": "admin",
        "category": "data_structures",
        "date": "2025-01-22 20:28:15",
        "score": 0,
        "questions": []
    },
    {
        "username": "islam",
        "category": "basics",
        "date": "2025-01-22 20:33:18",
        "score": 0,
        "questions": []
    },
    {
        "username": "islam",
        "category": "basics",
        "date": "2025-01-22 20:33:37",
        "score": 0,
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "Quel type de données est utilisé pour représenter du texte en Python ?",
                "user_response": "int",
                "correct_response": "str"
            },
            {
                "question": "What keyword is used to define a variable in Python?",
                "user_response": "var",
                "correct_response": "No keyword needed"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "username": "admin",
        "category": "basics",
        "date": "2025-01-22 20:43:38",
        "score": 1,
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "Quel type de données est utilisé pour représenter du texte en Python ?",
                "user_response": "str",
                "correct_response": "str"
            },
            {
                "question": "What keyword is used to define a variable in Python?",
                "user_response": "let",
                "correct_response": "No keyword needed"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "username": "islam",
        "category": "basics",
        "date": "2025-01-22 20:45:04",
        "score": 1,
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "Quel type de données est utilisé pour représenter du texte en Python ?",
                "user_response": "int",
                "correct_response": "str"
            },
            {
                "question": "What keyword is used to define a variable in Python?",
                "user_response": "var",
                "correct_response": "No keyword needed"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the output of '3 + 2 * 2' in Python?",
                "user_response": "10",
                "correct_response": "7"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of these is a valid Python identifier?",
                "user_response": "variable_1",
                "correct_response": "variable_1"
            }
        ]
    }
]